Mss.B.H357.p
American Philosophical Society
- Photographs, 25.0 Photograph(s)
  - Full length portrait of two girls, Kabayan, Benguet Province, Philippines., n. d.; U5-4-12; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group portrait of two girls in traditional attire, standing outside.
  - Full lenth portrait of man in uniform shirt and helmet, legs bare., U5-3-90; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full lenght portrait of man with beard and helmet, standing outside, hills in background.
  - Gen. Wood and Edward, Duke of Windsor., 1921; U5-3-50; 1.0 Photograph(s); 3/4 length candid portrait of Leonard Wood and Edward, Duke of Windsor walking outside, part of the Wood-Forbes Mission to Philippines, 1921.
  - Gen. Wood tipping his hat to a nurse, surrounded by unidentified men and women., 1921; U5-3-55; 1.0 Photograph(s); Leonard Wood, with party of men in uniform, tipping his hat in greeting to a nurse, part of the Wood-Forbes Mission to Philippines, 1921
  - Gen. Wood, with hand on child's head as a man in white addresses a crowd., 1921; U5-3-56; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group of people gathered, being addressed by an unidentified man in white suit, Leonard Wood has his hand on a child's head, part of Wood-Forbes Mission to Philippines, 1921.
  - Girl seated, wearing dress., n. d.; U5-4-34; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of girl seated, wering dress.
  - Group of men and one woman from Luzon., U5-3-166; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group portrait of men sitting and standing, one woman standing on the right, mountains in background.
  - Group portrait of adminstrative leaders of Philippines, including Hadji Mohammad Jamalul Kiram, Sultan of Sulu., 1914, September; U5-4-1; 1.0 Photograph(s); Eight men, sitting and standing, exterior wall of building in background.
  - Group portrait of Deputy Provincial Governor and other administrative leaders of Philippines., 1914, September; U5-4-2; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group portrait of men sitting and standing, exterior wall in background.
  - Group portrait of doctors and nurses seated with group of Igorot men standing behind., U5-3-174; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group portrait of seven woman and one man seated, with eight men standing, exterior wall of building in background.
    Hand written note on back of photograph: "Dr. and Mrs. Schafeiro [?]."
  - Group portrait of four women in dresses and two men., 1.0 Photograph(s); 3/4 length group portrait of men, women and one child standing outside.
  - Group portrait of Igorot men and women., U5-3-84; 1.0 Photograph(s); Igorot men and women, sitting and standing, outside, building in background.
  - Group portrait of inhabitants of the Island of Basilan, Zamboanga, 1914., 1914, September; U5-3-172; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group portrait of men and women sitting and standing, exterior wall of building in background.
  - Group portrait of men and women, seated and standing, exterior wall of building in backgound, Zamboanga, 1914., 1914, September; U5-3-171; 1.0 Photograph(s); Men and women, seated and standing, exterior wall of building in background.
    Additional information on individuals hand written on back of photograph.
  - Group portrait of trustees from Rockefeller Foundation at dedication of Peking Union Medical College, 1921., U5-4-170; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length group portrait of men standing outside of building.
  - Hadji Mohammad Jamalul Kiram, Sultan of Sulu, seated., 1914, September; U5-3-176; 1.0 Photograph(s); Formal half length portrait of the Sultan of Sulu, seate, exterior wall of building in background.
  - Haitian Commission with President Roy of Haiti., 1930; U5-4-158; 1.0 Photograph(s); President Roy of Haiti, W. C. Forbes and six other men, standing on steps outside of building.
  - Hearings before the Haitian Commission, 1930., U5-4-157; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group of men and women standing around table, American flag hanging against back wall.
  - Heiser and four unidentified people outside under stone arch., U4-4-99; 1.0 Photograph(s); Heiser standing with unidentified man and woman, two men sitting.
  - Heiser and Gen. Wood being greeted by a group of unidentified men., 1921, August 31; U5-3-51; 1.0 Photograph(s); Heiser, Wood and unidentified group of men standing outside, part of the Wood-Forbes Mission to Philippines, 1921.
    Hand written note on back of photograph: "The Wood-Forbes Mission and party in the Culwin (?) Leper Colony, Aug. 31, 1921.
  - Heiser and Ifugao man in traditional attire., U5-3-70; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length group portrait of Heiser and an unidentified Ifugao man standing outside, other people in background.
  - Heiser and others at the Imperial Institute for Infectious Diseases, Japan., U5-4-162; 1.0 Photograph(s); Heiser and group of other men standing outside of building.
  - Heiser and six other men at the Saiseikai Hospital (?), Japan (?)., U5-4-164; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length group portrait of Heiser and six other men standing outside, building in background.
  - Heiser and six unidentified men in academic robes, in procession, Peking Union Medical College., U5-4-168; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of Heiser and others walking in robes at the medical college.
  - Heiser and sixteen unidentified men at a meeting of the Far Eastern Association in Singapore., U5-3-35; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group portrait of the Far Eastern Association in Sinapore, taken on rooftop.
  - Heiser and three unidentified men standing in front of carved rock, Central America., U5-4-136; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length group portrait of Heiser and three men standing outside, carved rock behind them.
  - Heiser and two unidentified men standing outside., U4-5-40; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length portrait of Heiser and two men standing outside near tree and small wooden structure.
  - Heiser in tuxedo with unidentified man., n. d.; U5-3-32; 1.0 Photograph(s); Half length candid portrait of Heiser and unidentified man.
  - Heiser on horse at Bontoc, Philippines., n. d.; U4-5-21; 1.0 Photograph(s); Heiser sitting on horse in street, outside of building.
  - Heiser on horse, wearing hat., n. d.; U4-4-98; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length view of Heiser on horse back, building and trees in background.
  - Heiser seated at desk holding paper, 1943, 1943, June; U5-3-66; 1.0 Photograph(s); Half length view of Heiser, holding paper and pencil.
  - Heiser sitting outside on steps two men and three women., U5-3-74; 1.0 Photograph(s); Heiser seated on steps outside, with Mrs. Grant, Mrs. Tyler, Mr. Tyler, Dr. Grant Sr. and an unidentified woman.
  - Heiser standing next to guard., U5-3-69; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length view of Heiser and unidentified guard standing outside, fence and building in background.
  - Heiser standing on stone ledge of pyramid., U5-3-68; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length portrait of Heiser standing on stone ledge of pyramid.
  - Heiser wearing bow tie and holding hat under arm., U4-4-97; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length portrait of Heiser standing outside, trees in background.
  - Heiser, Dr. Peter and Dr. Cut (?) standing outside., 1922, March 19; U5-3-77; 1.0 Photograph(s); 3/4 length group portrait of Heiser, Peter and Cut (?), latter in foreground.
  - Heiser, William Gogas and unidentified man, wearing surgical masks, Guatemala., U5-4-139; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length group portrait of Heiser, Gorgas and another man standing, wearing masks, plants in background.
    Hand written note on back: "With Gen. Gorgas in Guatemala during a flu epidemic."
  - Heiser, William Gorgas and one unidentified man, seated., U5-4-137; 1.0 Photograph(s); Heiser and two unidentified men sitting in chairs, plants in background.
  - Heiser, William Gorgas and two unidentified men horse back., U5-4-138; 1.0 Photograph(s); Heiser, Gorgas and two unidentified men, on horses, surrounded by plants in Central America.
  - Heiser, with Hoover's Commission to Haiti., n. d.; U5-4-155; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group portrait of Heiser and six other men standing on steps outside of building.
    Hand written note on back: "With Hoover's Commission to Haiti."
  - Home of a prisoner settler, Iwahig, Plawan Province, Philippines., n. d.; U5-4-27; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of five unidentified men standing outside of a structure.
  - Ifugao Igorot women, Neuva Vizcaya., n. d.; U5-3-170; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length view of two women, bare chested, sitting on a stone structure, one woman touching the other woman's hair.
  - Ifugao women dancing, Nueva Vizcaya., U5-3-169; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length view of two Ifugao women dancing, crowd of people in background.
  - Igorot man standing outside holding spear and shield., U5-3-162; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length portrait of Igorot man holding spear and shield.
  - Ilongot man with bow full drawn., n. d.; U5-4-8; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full lenght view of Ilongot man with bow, outside, trees in background.
  - Inaugural session of the 30th annual meeting of the Philippine Island Medical Association., 1932, December 13; U5-3-60; 1.0 Photograph(s); Heiser and six other men sitting on stage.
  - Inauguration of Provincial Government, Zamboanga, Philippines, September 1, 1914, 1914, September 1; U5-3-36; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of speaker addressing three standing men and a crowd of seated officials.
    Additional information concerning the individuals present is handwritten on back of photograph.
  - Jars of tapuy, Cervantes, Lepanto, Philippines., n. d.; U5-4-32; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of jars on ground with crowd standing behind them.
  - Madallom and Lieutenant Gilfillan, Lubuagan Province., U5-3-168; 1.0 Photograph(s); Man and uniform and Filipino man in traditional attire sitting on ground with a gramophone between them.
  - Main entrance to San Ramon Prison., 1914, September; U5-4-7; 1.0 Photograph(s); Exterior view of prison entrance, man standing in entrance way, American flag on top of building.
  - Man dancing before a crowd, Zamboanga, 1914, 1914, September; U5-4-3; 1.0 Photograph(s); Man dancing on blanket, crowd watching.
  - Man from Jolo Province, Philippines, standing outside building., U5-4-5; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length portrait of man in traditional attire.
  - Moro boys and girls in boats surrounded by water., U5-4-6; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of several boats with and people in a body of water.
  - Mr. O. K. Tyler (?), standing outside., U5-3-80; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length portrait of Tyler (?) holding carabao horns (?).
  - Nine unidentified men standing outside building., 1921; U5-3-39; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length group protrait of nine men standing outside. Part of the Wood-Forbes mission to the Philippines, 1921.
  - Officials of the Mountain Province, Bontoc., n. d.; U5-3-167; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group portrait of fourteen men, sitting and standing, outside wearing hats, exterior wall of building in background.
  - President of Lubo (?) and his wife, Bontoc, Philippines., U5-4-30; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length portrait of man and woman, bare chested, standing outside, mountains in background.
    Title taken from printed inscription on back of photograph.
  - Procession of men riding carabao., 1921; U5-3-54; 1.0 Photograph(s); Line of mounted carabao on dirt road, part of the Wood-Forbes Mission to Philippines, 1921.
  - Profile of Igorot man, Bontoc Province, Philippines., n. d.; U5-4-19; 1.0 Photograph(s); Half length formal portrait in profile of Igorot man.
  - Seven Igorot men standing outside on steps, U4-5-20; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length group portrait, building in background.
  - Sultan of Sulu, Princess of Sulu, Sultans wife and other officials and high ranking women of Sulu., 1914, September; U5-4-18; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group portrait of seven women and two men standing and sitting, exterior wall of building in background.
  - Tea party in honor of Heiser, Manila, 1931., 1931, January 21; U5.3.62; 1.0 Photograph(s); Heiser at a table with seven women.
  - The "Three Muskateers" of the Haitian Commission., 1930; U5-4-160; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length group portrait of Forbes, Vezina (?) and White (?) of the Haitian Commission, standing outside.
    Title taken from hand written note on back of photograph.
  - Three Igorot women holding baskets., n. d.; U5-3-165; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length group portrait of three women, two bare chested, holding baskets on their heads.
  - Three men standing outside in uniform, building in background., 1921; U5-3-52; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length group portrait of three men standing outside, part of the Wood-Forbes Mission to Philippines, 1921.
  - Tucucan (?) delegation of Plaza at Bontoc., U5-4-26; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of native Filipino men and women in traditional attire sitting and standing outside, building and another group of people in background.
    Title taken from printed text on back of photograph.
  - Two young girls working on loom, Benguet Province, Philippines., n. d.; U5-4-11; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of two girls working on loom, outside, plants in background.
  - Tyler and an unidentified Igorot man., U5-3-161; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full lenght group portrait of Tyler, hoding bananas and wearing hat, and an unidentified Igorot man, standing outside.
  - View of audience for the inaugural session of the 30th annual meeting of the Philippine Islands Medical Association., 1932, December; U5-3-61; 1.0 Photograph(s); Large crowd sitting, windows in background.
  - View of body of water with boats, one with pro-American sign., 1921; U5-3-53; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of water with several boats, one boat in foreground has American Flag and pro-America sign, part of the Wood-Forbes Mission to the Philippines, 1921
  - View of hands of man with leprosy, U5-4-108; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of hands of man who suffers from leprosy.
    Hand written note on back of photograph: "Hands of a leper. This man is not able to straighten finger of left hand."
  - View of hillside with running men., n. d.; U5-4-23; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of hillside with men running to a focal point near center of photograph.
  - View of large gathering with unidentified man standing, addressing the crowd., 1921; U5-3-58; 1.0 Photograph(s); Gathering associated with the Wood-Forbes Mission to the Philippines, 1921.
  - View of Panama Canal., n. d.; U4-5-41; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of Panama Canal showing locks.
  - View of procession of Heiser and unidentified men dressed in academic robes, in procession, Peking Union Medical College., U5-4-169; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of procession leaving building and entering courtyard.
  - View of seven people sitting on ground beside a small structure., U4-5-19; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group of people sitting on ground beside a small structure made of plants.
  - View of the botanical garden, Manila., n. d.; U5-4-22; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of grounds with two men and one woman standing outside, buildings and plants in background.
  - Visiting President Borno of Haiti., 1930, March; U5-4-156; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of room with semi-circle of chairs set up with men seated.
  - W. Cameron Forbes (?) shaking hands with unidentified man in crowd., 1921; U5-3-42; 1.0 Photograph(s); Forbes (?), with officials in uniform behind him, shaking hands with unidentified man, part of the Wood-Forbes Mission to Philippines, 1921
  - W. Cameron Forbes (?) shaking hands with unidentified man., 1921; U5-3-41; 1.0 Photograph(s); Half length view of two men, one in hat, one in uniform, shaking hands outside, during the Wood-Forbes Mission to Philippines, 1921.
  - W. Cameron Forbes and group of men walking down dirt road., 1921; U5-3-57; 1.0 Photograph(s); Forbes and party of men in suits and uniforms walking outside on dirt road, between buildings, part of Wood-Forbes Mission to Philippines, 1921.
  - Young girl working on loom, Benguet Province, Philippines., n. d.; U5-4-10; 1.0 Photograph(s); Girl sitting, working on loom.